<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HearingAid</string>
    <string-array name="genders">
        <item>Select a Gender</item>
        <item>Male</item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="Page1">
    <![CDATA[
    <p>Find a Quiet Place Before you Start the Test. Try to lessen the amount of noise around you.</p>
    <p>You can turn on Do Not Disturb, so you don’t receive notifications and calls during the Hearing Test.</p>
    <p>Please Turn off Audio Effects such as Active Noise Cancellation as these may affect the accuracy of the test.</p>
    <p>The test only takes ~ 5 minutes.</p>
    ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="Page2">The tone will play automatically the first time and the frequency will increase automatically until you press \n \" Can Hear\" or \" Can\'t Hear\".</string>
    <string name="Page3">The test will run for each ear, shown by the button color and headphone. Blue means active and Grey means inactive. Left ear first, then right.</string>
    <string name="Page4">Press the Play button to play the tone and Press the Stop button to stop the test at any given time. Stopping the test will not save any test results.</string>
    <string name="HearSignal">Can you hear the signal?</string>
    <string name="test_history">Test History</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help_page">HelpPageActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    //Help Page
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to the Hearing Aid App!</string>
    <string name="welcome_description">This app allows you to use it as a hearing aid better hearing quality.</string>
    <string name="noise_suppression_mode">1. Noise Suppression Mode</string>
    <string name="noise_suppression_modes_explanation">Choose between On and Off using the radio buttons.\nOn: Noise suppression is active, reducing background noise.\nOff: Noise suppression is disabled.</string>
    <string name="gain_control">2. Gain Control</string>
    <string name="gain_control_explanation">Gain adjusts the Volume. Slide the seek bar to the right to increase and to the left to decrease the volume.</string>
    <string name="start_and_stop_button_explanation">Use the START button to activate the Audio Playback (Hearing Aid) feature. Press the Stop button to stop it.</string>

</resources>